-Will this be a good shot?
-Happy boy.
Hey Mister Turtle!
-Turtle, give her kiss.
Turtle gimme kiss.
-Aww. Good boy.
Sweet baby.
Hello...
-Okay. Positions!
Oh, right... Where do you want me?
-Um okay so what.
What?
-What's about to happen?
Umm, I'm gonna watch Game of Thrones for the first time.
*Dramatic music*
-Erm, have you never seen an episode ever?
Nope.
-What do you think it's about?
Okay so... Some chick has sex with dragons.
and there's wolves involved at some point.
-Mhmm
and on Bob's Burgers there were zombie things
which bored people to death, so I'm guessing there must be zombie things...Right?
Oh! There's a magical chair
Made out of pointy things, which people sit on like a bed of nails.
-Uh-huh...
but they don't die.
-No
Which makes no logical sense
because that would really hurt...
*Gasps*Oh! It's called Game of Thrones!
So- Everyone wants the chair
-Because it's  really nice accessory piece for the front room.
-Mhmm
But
Er... They have to play a game to get it?
-What do you know about the show and the characters?
Jon Snow is in it, chicks seem to dig him...
There's a big fat guy in it.
-Mhmm
Er... Don't know his name.
Ah, someone says Hodor a lot, or Ho-Door or
Prostitute door, or something.
-mhmm
-That was a good ho joke- ho pun.
Um. Yeah, yeah.
And. Oh! Khaleesi is a person and she is Queen of Dragons.
Which I'm guessing means that she has sex with the most dragons.
-Why have you never watched the show?
I wanted to read all of the books first
but there are too many books
-Oh! Where are we starting?
Er... Season Six?
Yes?
-Yes
Yes
Okay um. Someone's going to die
because apparently that happens a lot.
And there will be dragons.
-Do you think you're going to like the show?
-Do you anticipate...
I mean, I'm starting it at Season Six,
So probably not.
-Okay.
No. I don't think I'm gonna like the show.
*Slightly less dramatic music plays*
*Loud horse noises*
"Every day; every night."
*Dramatic panting*
*bad English accent*
"...anytime soon."
*tall woman screaming*
-So.
-Uh...
*sigh*
-You uh, took notes.
I did.
-Pages and pages of notes.
Yup. Lots of notes.
-Tell us what happened in the episode.
Oh, where do I start?
Okay.
So.
In a mystical land
with no barbers.
We find a dead bloke.
Takes 'em quite a while to find him
As you can tell by the amount of blood in the Snow.
But they decided to take him inside
"Jon Snow"
so that his body can start decomposing.
At first you're like, "I don't know if they are going to make him come
back to life or not."
And then they don't. They just do the eye close thing.
He got killed because he let Northerners in.
And apparently they suck.
Everyone likes a certain 'nice watch'.
That was very confusing.
-It is a very nice watch.
I don't know why you're laughing. It's true.
They kept talking about the nice watch.
I was very confused.
I'm assuming that at some point, Tony Snark..
Tony Stark is going to show up.
Because they kept talking about that.
Oh! They like having chandeliers everywhere.
But they are never lit.
Because they like dark rooms.
Oh! There was a suicide pact in the last...
*dramatic jumping music*
...season.
But it didn't work because they survived.
And then they were running away from people.
-Who...who is 'they'?
A bloke who looked like a disturbed version of Luke Skywalker
And a red-headed chick.
There's an evil king who likes to cut off weiners.
And apparently everyone likes cutting off bits of bodies.
And then...
Uh, the angry lesbian came and chopped a bunch of people up.
*Angry Lesbian screaming*
Apparently Peter Dinklage didn't murder the incest child king.
And so people don't like him for some reason.
Uh, people in Game of Thrones can't make speeches.
"...for yours if need be"
Probably don't invite them to a wedding anytime soon.
because they would do a terrible, terrible job.
There was this red-headed chick and she was standing up
And then the Butch Lesbian Angry Chick was kneeling down.
And I'm not sure if she was being knighted because she was already wearing knight clothes.
But the... the Red-Headed chick was trying really hard to make a speech
And she sucked.
"That you should always have a place by my...
*awkward stuttering*
"Meet and mead at my table."
Apparently a brother did a sister and produced the Incest King.
And yes there are barbers, they just don't like the snow
because in the sunny area
everyone had short hair.
Right?
The desert people that had the slaves are all styled by System of A Down.
Which I thought was quite nice
because they need work nowadays.
Oh, in the snow place
It appears that everyone there is a part of a
Norwegian, Death Metal cover band.
I say this because their hair is like this long,
and it's straight, and they all look really grumpy all the time.
The red woman is not another name for a woman's period.
and thus-forth, Game of Thrones is not a period piece
and when you take off your necklace, you get old wrinkly boobs.
-What were your first impressions of the show?
It was very slow moving
It was very confusing when they switched between places
because like, er, just it was- seemed like they were switching seasons
almost, which I didn't like.
Why didn't they light the chandeliers?
-Were there any, er, things you liked about the show?
*awkward silence*
Um...
I liked the butch lesbian, 'cause she kicked a few butts
*dramatic music/butt kicking noises*
I mean the scenery was nice
I liked that. It was quite pretty.
Do you remember anybody's name?
Yes, I found out that Jon Snow isn't the actor's name
That's the name of the character.
and...
er... No.
-What are your predictions for the next episode?
Someone's going to die.
Hopefully Khaleesi won't have to go into the place that they were trying to put her in to.
because they said they were going to put her in some scary place.
and then they'll get eaten by dragons.
That that wolf dog thing is gonna eat some people
'cause he just looked really hungry for human flesh,
and
Oh, that red-haired chick's probably gonna die
'cause she clearly has pneumonia at this point.
No-one survives wading through ice water,
and then sitting in the snow, and then sitting in some more snow,
and then standing in the snow without getting at least some form of pneumonia.
and they clearly don't have the medicine for that.
'cause they don't even have a barber.
-Why do you think the, er, whole world is obsessed with this show?
I have absolutely no idea...
I think it's because they can't make another 'Lord of the Rings' movie...
and I mean, er...
they could have just made this into films...
they should have compiled them
and made really long, really interesting films...
and just left it at that...
I have no idea why people are so obsessed with this show.
No clue...
Sorry.